I (CONTINUES SINGING) I
(Stuart:)I'll stop now.
(Amy(tablet ringing):)How's it going, Sheldon?
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)That's it.
(Sheldon:)The baby's here.
(Sheldon:)It's a boy.
(Leonard:)Congrats.
(Sheldon:)Oh, thank you.
(Sheldon:)I wasn't sure I was
going to make it.
(Sheldon:)But my mother
gave me some ice chips,
my sister told me to breaths.
(Sheldon:)And I just thought
to myself "Sheldon,
(Sheldon:)if you can make it through
the Green Lantern movie,
you can make it through this. "
(Leonard:)Well, good for you, buddy.
(Leonard:)We'll let you get back in there.
(Sheldon:)No, no, I'm not
going back in there.
(Sheldon:)That baby is so irritating.
(Sheldon:)He has literally been crying
his entire life.